"Clear" Mahjong?
Designated yaku
The team that clears them first, wins
If that's your gut feeling
It's okay.
I'll take it
Ron.
SanAnKou cleared
A head pair?
Could I get a chitoitsu like this?
The alternative is a called Tanyao
Chii
Pon
Soga's without doubt in Tenpai
According to his discards...
his wait is most probably
3, 6, or 9 Pin?
I'm in Tenpai
But, it's one step too late
If I had reached Tenpai just one turn earlier
Ten could have dealt me a 6 Pin
but in the current situation
a 6 Pin is Soga's winning tile
He'd Head Bump
Dealing in is impossible
やつは今
Now this guy
しくじりながらも懸命になんとかしようとしている
Failure while doing utmost effort doing
その意気に賭けよう
betting on that spirit
There's most probably still one 6 Pin left to draw
He got it
With that last draw the Kid's hand is ready
If you consider his Chitoitsu fell apart...
he's waiting on this very 6 Pin or a 9 Pin
but the character is aiming for a Tanyao
and right now he can't win off a 6 Pin
according to his discards, Ten certainly has a 6 Pin
But he's read Soga's wait
and he can't deal into it
The kid's Tanyao is nipped in the bud
The only remaining ways he could win
winning off the last draw or the last discard
I'll erase those hopes as well!
Chii
It's over
there's two more turns
but this hand is already done
entering Tenpai on a 9 Pin edge tile
9 Pin is the kid's winning tile
and besides calling the final discard
the moron's got no Yaku
To the kid, this hand
will end with a no Tenpai penalty
1,500 or possibly decreased to 1,000 points
and if that happens in his current state
If that happens
If that happens losing 500 points is huge
Pon
He's still got those
Kan
A Rinshan replacement draw?
at any rate
That possibility is so godly slight
It's only natural
the natural conclusion
ひろゆき、
Hiroyuki,
実ったぞ
The fruit has ripened
はい
I understand
ripened?
what's he on about?
Kan
OH FUCK
Yes...
Ron
ChanKan, 3 Dora
8,000 points
Pon
That odd 9 Pin Pon
It wasn't a Pon call when he had two tiles
It was a Pon call when he had THREE
The Kid, from Ten's hand
ひろゆき、
Hiroyuki,
生き延びたな
You survived
Yes, I did
Now Hiroyuki has a safety buffer
舐めた真似しよって
やられた
万全を尽くした天さんが敗れ、
一鉄を通した原田が勝った
すでにこの場は通常の定石確率は通用しない
間に合うのか
まずい、差し込まれたか
原田の手の速さを見たら欲張らず三色だけでも和了っておくべき。まだ原田は聴牌していない。天さんの待ちは恐らく索子の下辺り、天さんがツモるか俺が差し込めればこの局は勝てる
そうか、原田の三色、そもそもあれが目くらまし。やつらは三色など鼻から眼中にない
点棒で俺を脱落させるつもりだったんだ
こいつら
なんて事考えやがる
ちっ、気付いたか
きりそうな気配だったのに
よくぞ気付いた。ひろゆき
こいつら、
またせこい手を使いやがって
今は最終局面、
どんな手を使っても
勝たなきゃいかんのや
そのリーチ、
後悔させたるわ